Two Years Later:
Osaka
All Automatic Tables
Mahjong
New Maruko
It was two years later.
I left Tokyo, just wandering.
I found a life.
But here for half a year,
Instead I had not played Mahjong
REAL Mahjong.
Ron.
8,000 points.
That's his fifth consecutive win.
He's too strong.
息をするのもはばかられる緊張感
強烈な痺れるような麻雀
THAT Mahjong.
I noticed.気に入ったわ
あんさんみたいな打ち手を探しとったんや
ちょっと付き合ってや
An East/West Contest?
関東と関西のトップクラスの代打ちが集まって
An East/West Underground Mahjong Contest.
俺を西に引き込もうと？
Why is someone from Hiroshima doing here?
Because it's always without fail held in Osaka.
Because of our players didn't come from Tokyo
If that's the case the East side will win.
It's ain't so simple.
The West side has a monster.
Monster?
関西有力の暴力団の組長でありながら
代打ちでもある
原田克美
圧倒的な金と力と人脈で
有力なやつをスカウトしている
勝つとどうなるか
上納金の独占
Hunh?
勝った側が
全国に1万件ある雀荘を仕切るんや
1日1万円の上納金で1日1億円
間でおよそ
350億の金が入る
Sugoi.凄い
こっころ踊る話やろ
どや！？東の陣営に入らんか
Decide quick.
とりあえず俺の兄貴分にあってもらう
That's the Boss Ringer I told you about.
The West Team head, Harada Katsumi.
代打ちの中でも文句なしに最強の男
赤木の再来と言われる天才
東の大将は
わしの兄貴はそこの正面向いて麻雀打ってる
不敗の赤木に一度だけ土をつけた男
無類の勝負強さから数多くの不可能を可能にしてきた
東の頭
天貴史